# Khushbu Sharma

KhushbuSharma547@gmail.com @

919024853325

Near heerapura power House ,Ajmer road, Jaipur 💡

https://www.linkedin.com/in/khushbu-sharma- in

7a779416b

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a Hybrid Application developer for both Android and IOS with 4+ years experience. I have worked on PHP backends like CI and Laravel frameworks for building APIs.I am interested in making different products with different languages. I like when I work in backend web services like making API and also database queries. It's been 4+ years since I've been around development. I have done many projects in different technologies like Flutter, React Native, Ionic framework, Android, Web Application and also in php framework.

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

#### **EDUCATION**

University of maharani college

2013-2016 Bca

First division

# University of Rajasthan

2016-2019 MCA First division

### **EXPERIENCE**

Muray technology India private limited

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019 Web developer and designer Work as in core PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and also make APIs in PHP. CI and laravel.

#### Marketing mindz

Sept 2019 - Nov 2021 Hybrid Application developer Work as in web design and development, Ionic framework, React Native, Flutter for Android and IOS.

# Emizentech

Nov 2021 - Current Hybrid application developer Working as in Flutter for Android and IOS.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Flutter

Currently working on Flutter with 2.3 years experience.

#### **SKILLS**

Android and IOS(4 years experience)

Dart(Flutter with 2.2 years experience)

React native(1 year experience)

Ionic framework with typescript and angular(6 months experience)

Core Java(3 months experience)

PHP(CI and laravel),Html, Css, Bootstrap (8 months experience)

#### **TECHNICAL SKILL**

# Mobile platform for Android and IOS

Core Java, Ionic framework with typescript and angular, Android SDK, React Native, JavaScript, Flutter with dart.

Publish Android Application in Google Store and IOS Application on App Store.

Json database modeling and design

# **Mobile Libraries**

Camera API, Facebook SDK, Amazon Web Service, Firebase services and third party push notifications, Barcode and Qrcode, Google map SDK, Pdf download, REST APIs using Http, Third party APIs of magneto, Node, etc.

### **Databases**

MySql

#### Web technologies

Web services, Apache Tomcat, Json, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap APIs in CI, Laravel, Core PHP and React Js.

#### **Development Environments**

Android Studio, Visual Studio, Xcode, Intellij idea

#### **Other Tools**

Gitlab, Bitbucket, GitHub, GitDesktop, Figma, JIRA, Trello, Testflight

#### **Testing**

Manual and Unit testing.

#### Knowledge

C, C++, Scripting languages like Typescript. Some other knowledge in Swift language for IOS.

#### **PROJECTS**

### Cashew india App(Java project)

The app is developed under the program on Mission for Integrated Development of Horticulture (MIDH), Ministry of Agriculture and Farmers Welfare, Government of India.It gives information on cashew grafts, nursery, cultivation, plant protection, post harvest processing, market information, emarket, various stakeholders such as farmers, researchers, developmental agencies, processors at one place. Follow up this link for

Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cashew.icar&hl=en\_IN

### Mindz catalog App(Ionic project)

This project is for marketing mindz company which is based on catalog model describe to display categories and products.

Follow up this link for

Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mm.mindzcatalog&hl=en\_IN

los:-url:-https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mindz-catalog/id1514928521?ls=1

# Accuwatch App(Ionic project)

This app is based on an open label, single center, observational clinical evaluation study to asses the accuracy of a wearable device for vital sign monitoring as compared to the conventional digital devices Accuwatch. Follow up this link for

Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mm.ACCUWATCH&hl=en\_IN

### Calculot app (Ionic project)

This is based on 25 categories with different-different questions related to the user's current location and at the end generate a scorecard according to the answers. The user download the scorecard as pdf format.

### Arch paint (React native project)

This is based on estimation of painting. From New England's most trusted painting contractor comes the Arch Painting Estimator, a free app that allows home-owners to receive an estimate without having to meet with us face-to-face. Follow up this link

for Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.archpaint&hl=en\_IN

IOS: https://apps.apple.com/us/app/arch-painting-estimator/id1384848040

### Icar Mung advisor (React native project)

This is based on details of crop and site of Myanmar and available in two languages Burmese and English.

# Santaclauz App(Flutter project)

This app is based on E-commerce Kids toys and other things shopping app.

Follow up this link for Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=com.mm.santaclauz&hl=en\_IN

# Mamas first(Flutter project)

This is based on kids E-commerce application.
Follow up this link for
Android:https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?
id=com.mamasfirst

#### Richa Mart(Flutter project)

This is based on user and vender E-commerce application related to grocery.

# Bossonova(Flutter project)

This is based on mini market E-commerce application with barcode scanner product searching and get user live location to display the nearby stores.

### OTHER PROJECTS

### Mayur fashion website

This project is based on Traditional Rajputi Clothing and accessories website.

# Thekapdabazaar website

This project is related to listing website like as justdial.

# Fiyova junction application

This Android project is for cab driver and my work is on backend with admin panel.

#### Merayoga application

This Android project is based on yoga's videos and my work is on backend with admin panel.

### Astrology application

This Android project is related to astrology and my work is on backend with admin panel.

#### BlueCollar application

This Android project is for employees and employer and my work is on backend like apis.

# E-mall application

This Android project is for shopping and my work is on backend Apis.

# **INTERESTS**

Writing and reading poetries.

To participate new areas in Development.

Development of Applications and database queries.

To join Salesforce in future

# PERSONAL STRENGTH

Keep to learn new things.

Can work under pressure.

Helping nature and hard working in any circumstances.

Flexible to adopt any circumstances.

In-depth understanding of computer programming language and ability to code

Ability to think creatively and find unique solutions to problems

Active listening skills to truly hear feedback and incorporate notes effectively

# **ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS**

Certificate of (workshop on youth-n-democracy.

Co-scholastoc activities certificate.

Workshop on Google.

RSCIT certificate.

Online Ethical Hacking Workshop attend.